{
    "subject": "resource/Basketball_L\u00f6wen_Braunschweig",
    "predicate": "ontology/location",
    "object": "resource/Germany",
    "human_readable": "The location of Basketball L\u00f6wen Braunschweig is Germany.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9752453565597534,
            "question": "Name the country where Basketball L\u00f6wen Braunschweig is situated."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9562280178070068,
            "question": "Where is Basketball L\u00f6wen Braunschweig located?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9407795071601868,
            "question": "Is Germany the home country of Basketball L\u00f6wen Braunschweig?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9062783122062683,
            "question": "Is Basketball L\u00f6wen Braunschweig a German team?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8823721408843994,
            "question": "Where can you find Basketball L\u00f6wen Braunschweig?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7569994926452637,
            "question": "In what country is Basketball L\u00f6wen Braunschweig based?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.720460832118988,
            "question": "What is the nationality of Basketball L\u00f6wen Braunschweig?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5805685520172119,
            "question": "Is Basketball L\u00f6wen Braunschweig an international team?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5186820030212402,
            "question": "To which nation does Basketball L\u00f6wen Braunschweig belong?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4932430386543274,
            "question": "What sport does Basketball L\u00f6wen Braunschweig play?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The location of Basketball L\u00f6wen Braunschweig is Germany.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7603_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=To which nation does Basketball L\u00f6wen Braunschweig belong?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7603_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Basketball L\u00f6wen Braunschweig an international team?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7603_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the nationality of Basketball L\u00f6wen Braunschweig?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7603_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7603_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7603_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7603_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7603_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7603_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7603_49.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7603_55.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7603_75.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7603_80.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7603_84.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in the required format:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provided contain information about Basketball L\u00f6wen Braunschweig, including its location in Braunschweig, Germany. This supports the statement that the location of Basketball L\u00f6wen Braunschweig is Germany."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}